{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Porch \u0026 Gazebo Builders","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40348/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40348,"taskName":"Gazebo or Freestanding Porch - Build or Install","taskDescription":"Build or Install a Gazebo or Freestanding Porch","xmTaskDescriptor":"Porch \u0026 Gazebo Builders","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":101,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Gazebo custom construction free addition","textMessagingName":"Build Gazebo","rolloverLongDesc":"Either custom, a kit built onsite or a ready-made unit brought in by truck \u0026 installed onsite.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes pre-fab, kit \u0026 custom built models.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Build or Install a Gazebo or Freestanding Porch.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Build a Gazebo or Porch \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Porch \u0026 Gazebo Builders","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":37,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Gazebo Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Gazebo or Freestanding Porch - Build or Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Gazebo Project","urlName":"Gazebo-or-Freestanding-Porch-Build-or-Install","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Gazebo \u0026 Porch Builders - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Gazebo,custom,construction,free,addition,sun,steel,spa,pool,metal,tub,hot,outbuilding,building,out,enclosure,wood,Freestanding,Build,Porch","emcCategoryOid":-12063,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":642,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40348/":{"taskOID":40348,"originalTaskOID":40348,"setID":642,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4471,"questionDisplayText":"Gazebo Style","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What style of gazebo do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":203385,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Rectangular / Square","answerDisplayText":"Rectangular / Square","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4499,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Oval","answerDisplayText":"Oval","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4328,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Octagon (8-sided)","answerDisplayText":"Octagon (8-sided)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200054,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Not sure - Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Not sure - Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4473,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Deck/Floor","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of deck/floor?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4277,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"None-it will rest on existing deck/patio","answerDisplayText":"None-it will rest on existing deck/patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4836,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Poured concrete slab","answerDisplayText":"Poured concrete slab","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5020,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Raised deck with lattice","answerDisplayText":"Raised deck with lattice","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5024,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Raised solid deck","answerDisplayText":"Raised solid deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4474,"questionDisplayText":"Other Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What other features would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6461,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Traditional square picket walls","answerDisplayText":"Traditional square picket walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5896,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Solid walls","answerDisplayText":"Solid walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5766,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Skylight","answerDisplayText":"Skylight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1020,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bench(es)","answerDisplayText":"Bench(es)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6222,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Swing","answerDisplayText":"Swing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":940,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bar","answerDisplayText":"Bar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5506,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Screens","answerDisplayText":"Screens","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2001,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Door","answerDisplayText":"Door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2818,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Glass windows","answerDisplayText":"Glass windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1289,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Ceiling Fan","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling Fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2191,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Electricity","answerDisplayText":"Electricity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4741,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Plumbing","answerDisplayText":"Plumbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6090,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Stereo, TV, cable, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Stereo, TV, cable, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4471,"questionDisplayText":"Gazebo Style","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What style of gazebo do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":203385,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Rectangular / Square","answerDisplayText":"Rectangular / Square","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4499,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Oval","answerDisplayText":"Oval","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4328,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Octagon (8-sided)","answerDisplayText":"Octagon (8-sided)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200054,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Not sure - Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Not sure - Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":203385,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Rectangular / Square","answerDisplayText":"Rectangular / Square","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4499,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Oval","answerDisplayText":"Oval","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4328,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Octagon (8-sided)","answerDisplayText":"Octagon (8-sided)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200054,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Not sure - Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Not sure - Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4473,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Deck/Floor","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of deck/floor?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4277,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"None-it will rest on existing deck/patio","answerDisplayText":"None-it will rest on existing deck/patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4836,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Poured concrete slab","answerDisplayText":"Poured concrete slab","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5020,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Raised deck with lattice","answerDisplayText":"Raised deck with lattice","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5024,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Raised solid deck","answerDisplayText":"Raised solid deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4277,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"None-it will rest on existing deck/patio","answerDisplayText":"None-it will rest on existing deck/patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4836,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Poured concrete slab","answerDisplayText":"Poured concrete slab","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5020,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Raised deck with lattice","answerDisplayText":"Raised deck with lattice","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5024,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Raised solid deck","answerDisplayText":"Raised solid deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4474,"questionDisplayText":"Other Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What other features would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6461,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Traditional square picket walls","answerDisplayText":"Traditional square picket walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5896,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Solid walls","answerDisplayText":"Solid walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5766,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Skylight","answerDisplayText":"Skylight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1020,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bench(es)","answerDisplayText":"Bench(es)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6222,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Swing","answerDisplayText":"Swing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":940,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bar","answerDisplayText":"Bar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5506,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Screens","answerDisplayText":"Screens","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2001,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Door","answerDisplayText":"Door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2818,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Glass windows","answerDisplayText":"Glass windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1289,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Ceiling Fan","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling Fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2191,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Electricity","answerDisplayText":"Electricity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4741,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Plumbing","answerDisplayText":"Plumbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6090,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Stereo, TV, cable, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Stereo, TV, cable, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6461,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Traditional square picket walls","answerDisplayText":"Traditional square picket walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5896,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Solid walls","answerDisplayText":"Solid walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5766,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Skylight","answerDisplayText":"Skylight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1020,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bench(es)","answerDisplayText":"Bench(es)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6222,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Swing","answerDisplayText":"Swing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":940,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bar","answerDisplayText":"Bar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5506,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Screens","answerDisplayText":"Screens","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2001,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Door","answerDisplayText":"Door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2818,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Glass windows","answerDisplayText":"Glass windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1289,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Ceiling Fan","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling Fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2191,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Electricity","answerDisplayText":"Electricity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4741,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Plumbing","answerDisplayText":"Plumbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6090,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Stereo, TV, cable, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Stereo, TV, cable, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}